Travelling with Banjoko made it all feel different.
Of course he was not the first bird I met on my journey; migrants rarely get privacy.
But since I left home, that was the first time I felt someone truly understood me.
It was nice to have somebody to talk to, to laugh with, to discuss what we would do when we made it to Europe.
We had so many plans. We both really wanted to go to England, we even joked about sharing a nest one day.
It felt like we had always known each other. Hardship makes you bond faster, I guess.
Suddenly, I forgot why I had decided to leave home. After the Sahara, Europe was just so easy to enjoy.
We travelled short distances, taking the time to eat and rest. We crossed borders, always heading North.
It was a beautiful spring and there was plenty of food everywhere.
We felt happy. We felt safe.
Of course, we knew there were still dangers.
We had heard the tales of other travellers, the stories of birds getting lost, starving to death, dying of diseases or being shot by hunters.
But somehow, we believed this could not happen to us.
Because together, we felt invincible.
And together we were.